**UE4** Generalist Programmer

diegogaldamez08@gmail.com +503 75860071 Villas Escalon norte, #10 i, San Salvador, El Salvador.

# Diego Galdamez

# UE4 GENERALIST PROGRAMMER

### About me

I'm a generalist software developer. I started my carreer on the manufacturing industry, since the very early days I discovered my passion to the tech, I found myself working from engineering management to data analitics and everything in between always oriented to tech, I have knowledge in UE4 and Unity. I have experience on Python, PhP and Java Script.



Software

Unreal Engine 4, VS Code, Jupyter Notebook, Matlab.

Education

Chemical Engeneering degree (2011-2019)

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

September 2021 - Janaury 2022

Hanesbrand Inc. - La Libertad - El Salvador

### **QUALITY DATA ANALYST**

Review, consolidate and analyze production data for strategic decision making | Create and manage indicators in the quality department | Manage of digitalization project for quality data entry platform in production.

May 2019 - August 2021

La Constancia. - San Salvador - El Salvador

### MANAGEMENT STAFF ENGINEER

Manage KPIs for productive areas, analysis of weekly and monthly deviations | Creation and upload indicators dashboard | Deviations report | Support in the implementation of the VPO management system and support in the digital transformation.

September 2021 - Janaury 2022

La Constancia. - San Salvador - El Salvador

### MANAGEMENT STAFF ENGINEER

Follow up of process indicators and production efficiencies | Creation of a dashboard of indicators under the VPO management system | Deviations report | Monitoring of daily meetings.

### **OTHER STUDIES**

May 2021 Datacamp

### INTRODUCTION TO SQL

November 2020 - December 2020 Datacamp

### INTRODUCTION TO MACHINE LEARNING

December 2020 Datacamp

## DATA MANYPULATION WITH PANDAS (PYTHON)

October 2020 Datacamp

### **INTERMEDIATE PYTHON**